《迷失》前情提要
Previously on "Lost"
John  能拯救小岛的唯一方法
The only way to save the island,John,
就是让你们所有人都回岛上去
Is to get your people back here.
直升机要降落在船上  然后船...
The chopper was headed for the boat. The boat--
没事  他们都很好  John  他们已经到家了
No,they're fine,John, and they're already home.
所以你得去说服他们回来
So you have to convince them to come back.
怎么说  怎么把他们劝回来
How? How am I supposed to do that?
你得死掉  John
You're gonna have to die, John.
-你真要下去吗  -对
- You're going down there? - Uh-huh.
要不咱们应该怎么离开这个岛
What exactly are you hoping a way off the island?
等你把你那些朋友都找到
Once you get all of your friends together--
必须是每一个离岛的人  一个都不能少
and it must be all of them, everyone who left--
等你说服他们跟你走
once you've persuaded them to join you,
Eloise Hawking会具体告诉你怎么回岛
Eloise Hawking will tell you exactly how to come back.
Richard说我会死
Richard said I was going to die.
这就是所谓的牺牲
That's why they call it sacrifice.
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：  娜姬雅  锵锵  zerk  roseｍmryai   宝宝宝
校对：  娜姬雅  roseｍmryai  宝宝宝  七色九天  非燕  时间轴：雨中泪
■
后期：  冰蚕　　  剧集总监： 非燕
Caesar
Ilana
什么事
What's up?
找到什么了
Find anything?
没什么  没什么有价值的
No. Nothing useful.
那你刚才把什么装包里了
Then what'd you just put in your bag?
你想要就给你
If you want it, it's yours.
我们找到个人  是个男的
We found someone--a man.
什么
What?
Roxanne当时正在南边侦查
Roxanne was scouting just south of here,
那人就站在水里
And he was just standing in the water.
穿着西服
He's wearing a suit.
没人认识他吗
Nobody recognizes him?
没有  不管他是谁  他都不是我们的人
No. Whoever he is, he didn't come with us.
那我们怎么知道
Then how do we know he isn't one of
他是否属于失踪人员
The ones who disappeared?
-他不是  -你又怎么知道
- He's not. - And how do you know?
因为他没在飞机上
Because he wasn't on the plane.
这人有什么要说的吗
What did this man have to say?
你自己问
You can ask him yourself.
你好
Hello.
我叫Caesar
My name is Caesar.
你叫什么
What's yours?
我叫John Locke
My name is John Locke.
早啊
Morning.
你好
Hello.
吃早饭吗
Breakfast?
我们找到一棵树  果子挺好
We found a tree. They're pretty good.
非常感谢
Much obliged.
我叫Ilana
I'm Ilana.
我叫John
John.
那些是你们的船吗
Are those your boats?
不是  它们本来就在那
No. They were already here.
原来是3艘
There used to be three,
但是飞行员和几位女士划走了一艘
But the pilot and some woman took one.
他们谁也没告诉
Didn't tell anyone,
直接在半夜划走的
Just ran off in the middle of the night.
就是你们那趟航班的飞行员吗
The pilot of the plane that brought you here?
对  就是他
Yes. that's right.
你们有乘客名单吗
Do you have a passenger list?
你得跟Caesar要
You'll have to talk to Caesar.
我觉得这是我吃过的最甜的芒果
I think this is the best mango I've ever eaten.
谁也不记得你跟我们是同趟航班
Nobody remembers you being on the plane.
是吗  我自己也不记得
Well,I don't remember being on it either.
-那你记得什么  -那可多了
- What do you remember? - I remember a lot.
比如为什么穿得西装革履
Like why you're dressed up so nice?
不记得  但是我可以猜
No,but I can guess.
那就  猜猜吧
Please. Guess.
我觉得这身西服
I think this suit
是我入土的寿衣
Is what they were gonna bury me in.
你说什么
Sorry?
你问我记得什么
You asked what I remembered.
我记得我死了
I remember dying.
祝你好运  John
Good luck,John.
给我儿子带个好
Say hello to my son.
你儿子是谁
Who's your son?
突尼斯
Tunisia
有人吗  能不能帮帮我
Is anybody in there?! Can you help me?!
喂
Hey!
别走  喂
No! Hey!
喂
Hey!
啊  上帝啊
Aah! God!
啊  天啊
这是哪儿  我这是在什么地方
Where is this?  Where am I?
我这是在哪儿  这是什么地方
Where am I? Where is this?
大夫  我在哪儿  你是谁
Sir,where am I? Who are you?
我在哪儿  你会说英语吗
Where am I? Do you speak English?
吞下去
You swallow.
吞
Swallow.
咬
Bite!
咱们这是在哪
Where are we?
哦  怎么了  干嘛
Oh--What? What?
-干什么  干嘛  -咬住
- What? What-- - You bite.
John
John  醒醒
John,wake up.
你骨折了
You had a compound fracture.
这里医生已经尽最大努力
The doctors here did their best,
但我还是叫专家飞过来
But I had a specialist flown in
好好给你接腿
To reset your leg properly.
再见到你真高兴  John
It's nice to see you again,John.
我们见过吗
Do I know you?
见过
Yes.
我知道你现在糊涂了
I understand your being confused.
知道我的感受吗
Imagine how I feel.
认识你的时候  我才17岁
I met you when I was 17.
过了这么多年  我们又重逢了
And now all these years later, here we are.
你一点都没变
You look exactly the same.
你是谁
Who are you?
我叫Charles Widmore
My name is Charles Widmore.
告诉我  John
Tell me,John
从我们第一次见面  你那边已经过了多久了
How long has it been for you since... we first met,
从你走进我们的营地
Since you walked into our camp
和Richard谈话开始
And you spoke to Richard?
四天
Four days.
这真难以想象
That’s incredible.
沙漠里的摄像机是你的吗
The camera in the desert, that was yours?
是的
Yeah.
你怎么知道我在那里
How did you know I'd be there?
因为那里是出口
Because that's the exit.
我恐怕
I was afraid
Benjamin会骗你离开那个岛
Benjamin might fool you into leaving the island
就像他对我所做的
Like he did with me.
我是他们的领导
I was their leader.
其他人吗？
The others?
他们对我来说不是"其他人"  我们是一样的
They’re not the "others" to me. they're my people.
我们平静地保卫着这个小岛
We protected the island peacefully
有三十多年了
For more than three decades.
但后来我被放逐了
But then I was exiled
被他...
By him...
就像你一样
Just as you were.
不  我离开的时候Ben不在那里
No. Ben wasn't even there when i left.
他已经走了  我不是被放逐的
He was already gone. I, I... I wasn't exiled.
我... 选择离开
I... chose to leave.
你为什么要那么做？
Why... would you do that, John?
你要把他们带回来
You’ve come to bring them back...
那些离开的人
The ones who left.
不  不
No. .
你说的不是实话  我确信
I understand you lying to me. I do.
但是你应该知道
But there's something you should know.
你那些离开小岛的朋友们
All your friends who left the island
他们已经回来三年了
They’ve been back three years.
三年？
Three years?
他们回归了正常的生活
And they've gone back to their normal lives.
但没有一个人对发生的事情说了实话
And none of them has spoken a word of truth
也没说他们当时在哪
About where they were.
我得把他们带回来
I have to bring them back.
我会尽我所能帮助你的
I'm gonna do everything in my power to help you do that.
为什么？
Why?
什么为什么？
"Why"?
你为什么要帮我？
Why would you help me?
因为有场战争要来了  John
Because there's a war coming, John.
如果它发生的时候你还没有回到小岛
And if you're not back on the island when that happens,
邪恶的一方会胜利
The wrong side is going to win.
Jeremy Bentham是谁？
"Jeremy Bentham"?
一个英国哲学家
He was a British philosopher.
你父母给你了个幽默的名字
Your parents had a sense of humor when they named you,
所以为什么我不能这么做
So why can't I?
这些钱够你用了
This should be money enough for now.
这电话可以全球通话
The phone's international.
如果你有任何需要联系我
If you need to reach me, for anything,
拨23
Just press 23.
档案里有你们人的行踪
The folder contains your people's whereabouts,
所有曾经在岛上又离开的人
Everyone that was on the island that left.
你一直监视着他们
You’ve been watching them?
我对那个岛的未来投资了很多  John
I'm deeply invested in the future of the island, John.
所以是的  我监视了他们
So, yes, I've been watching them.
我不会与这事扯上联系
I wouldn't mention I'm involved in this.
很难想象他们会怎么看我
I can't imagine what they think of me,
尤其是被Benjamin的谎言迷惑后
Having listened to Benjamin's lies.
我怎么知道你不是在撒谎
How do I know that you're not the one who's lying?
我没有想要杀你
I haven't tried to kill you.
你和他也说了同样的话吗
Would you say the same for him?
你还是不相信我
You still don't trust me.
你派了群杀手去那个岛上
You sent a team of killers
还有一船的炸药
And a boatload of c4 to the island.
那不叫信任
That... doesn't exactly scream "trust."
我需要Linus离开那里
I needed Linus removed...
所以你可以发挥了
So it could be your time.
没错
Right.
那个岛需要你  John
The island needs you, John.
很长一段时间来
It has for a long time.
是什么让你觉得我如此特殊？
What makes you think I'm so special?
因为你本来就特殊
Because you are.
你的战车来了
Ah. your chariot has arrived.
他说我要死了
He said I would die.
-能再说一遍吗  -Richard Alpert
- I beg your pardon? - Richard Alpert.
他说只有我死了他们才能回去
He said only way to get them to come back was if I died.
我不知道他为什么这么说
I don't know why he said that,
但我不会让那发生的
But I'm not gonna let that happen.
这是Matthew Abaddon
This is Matthew Abaddon.
他会带你去任何地方
He’ll take you anywhere you need to go,
保护你
Protect you from whomever intends to do you harm.
Locke先生
Mr. Locke.
祝你们好运John  还有要快
Good luck, John, and Godspeed.
Locke先生  有什么需要的尽管告诉我
Anything you need, Mr. Locke, you just let me know.
任何事情
Anything.
你需要我帮你找什么老朋友吗
Anybody from your past you want me to look up for you?
Locke先生  全世界都认为你死了
The whole world thinks you're dead, Mr. Locke.
会有一些人高兴见到你的
There must be somebody who'd be happy to see you.
-请别和我说话  -好吧
- Please don't talk to me.  - You got it.
但我们已经差不多到机场了
But we're almost at the airport,
所以你至少告诉我去哪里
So you at least have to tell me where we're going first.
圣多明各
Santo Domingo.
圣多明各  多米尼加共和国
Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic
[西班牙语]
Sayid
Hey, Sayid!
Mira
Mira!
[西班牙语]
我不相信
I don't believe this.
你真的想让我回去
You actually want me to go back?
我知道这很荒谬  但你要相信我
I know how it sounds, Sayid, but you have to trust me.
-这是救他们的唯一办法了  -我不会回去的
- This is the only way to save them. -I'm not going back.
两年来  我已经习惯去思考
For two years, I was manipulated into thinking
-我在保护岛上所有人  -谁在操纵你
- I was protecting everyone on the island. - Who was manipulating you?
Ben
Ben.
那么谁在操纵你  John
So who is manipulating you, John?
是我自己的决定  不关其他人的事
this is coming from me, nobody else.
我了解你  Sayid
I know you, Sayid.
而且你深知
And deep down in your heart,
我们根本就不该离开小岛
you know we never should've left the island.
就是因为我离开了小岛
It's only because I left the island
我才能最终娶到我心爱的女人
that I was finally able to marry the woman I loved.
我们共度了九个月
we spent nine months together--
一生中最美好的九个月  John
the best nine months of my life,John.
那才是我内心的想法
that's what i know in my heart.
那她现在在哪里
where is she now?
她被人杀害了
she was murdered.
我很难过
i'm sorry.
你为什么非要回去
why do you really need to go back?
仅因为你别无他处可去吗
Is it just because you have nowhere else to go?
如果你改了主意
If you change your mind,
我会在洛杉矶维斯特菲尔德酒店等你
i'll be staying under the name "Jeremy Bentham"
我登记的名字是Jeremy Bentham
in l.a. at the westerfield hotel.
如果你改主意
And if you change your mind,
我们欢迎你回到这里做正事
you're welcome to come back here and do some real good.
再见  John
Good-bye, John.
纽约
New York，NY
-你问过是否能为我找到某人  -是的
- You asked if there was someone you could look up for me. - Yes, I did.
我要找Helen  Helen Norwood
Her name is helen-- helen norwood--
住在洛杉矶
and she was living in los angeles.
她是你的前女友吗
She an old girlfriend of yours?
把我弄下车
Help me get out of the car.
那就是Michael Dawson的儿子吗
So that's michael dawson's son,huh?
就是
Yeah.
都长这么大了
Boy's gotten big.
-我去去就来  我走了  -好的
- um,i'm--i'm-a be right back. i'm-a go.  - all right.
-我待会就回来  -好的
- i'm-a be right back.  - all right.
你们单独聊吧
i'll give you two some privacy.
好啊 John
hey,john.
好啊 Walt
hi,walt.
你怎么了
what happened?
我的腿受伤到
i hurt my leg.
似乎看到我  你并不惊讶呀
you don't seem surprised to see me.
我梦到过你
i've been having dreams about you.
你在岛上  穿了件西装
you were on the island, wearing a suit,
有好多人围着你
and there are people all around you.
他们想要伤害你  John
they wanted to hurt you, john.
幸好是个梦而已
good thing they're just dreams.
我爸爸...
is my dad...
他回到岛上了吗
is he back on the island?
我已经三年没见到他了
i haven't talked to him in three years.
我想他肯定回去了
i figured he must've gone back.
我最后听到关于他的消息是
um,last i heard,
他在岛附近的一艘货船上
your dad was on a freighter near the island.
那么你来找我干什么
so why'd you come to see me?
我只是想看看你是否过得好
i just wanted to make sure you were okay.
很好
yeah.
我挺好的
i'm doing pretty good.
我得走了  很高兴见到你  John
well,i gotta go. it was good seeing you,john.
我也是  保重
yeah. take care.
我看你是不会邀他一起去了
I take it you didn't invite him along.
他已经经历了够多了
Boy's been through enough.
已经有两个人不干  Locke先生
That's 0-for-2, Mr. Locke.
或许是我理解错了
maybe i misunderstood,
但我想你得带回所有人
but i thought you had to bring everyone back.
我只要说服一个人
i only need to convince one.
只要我说服了他  那其他的人自然会跟来
and if i can do that, the rest will come.
或许是我搞错了
and maybe i was mistaken,
我以为你只是我的司机而已
but i thought you we my driver.
圣罗莎  加利福尼亚
你好 Hugo
hello, hugo.
看来你没成功啊?
So you didn't make it,huh?
什么意思
pardon me?
你没成功
you didn't make it.
放心  没什么大不了
it's cool. no biggie.
你不是第一个来看我的人
you're not the first person to visit me,you know.
你怎么坐在轮椅上了
but what's up with the wheelchair?
我掉进洞里摔伤了腿
uh,i broke my leg falling down a hole.
你就是那么死的
oh. is that how you died?
Hugo  我没有死
hugo,i'm not dead.
你当然没有
sure you're not.
我发誓  我真的活着
no,i-i promise you, i'm very much alive.
Susie
hey,susie,
-我在和一个坐在轮椅上的人聊天吗  -有啊
- Am i talking to a dude in a wheelchair right now? - Yep.
我的天  老兄  你来做什么
whoa, dude. what are you doing here?
我要你跟我回岛上去
i need you to come back to the island with me.
等等  什么意思?
wait. what?
不止你一个人  所有离开的人都要回去
and not just you, but everybody who left.
-你是说Jack  Kate  -所有人
-you mean jack and kate... -everybody.
不好意思  老兄
i'm sorry,dude.
我想大家不会回去的
i don't think that's gonna happen.
Jack现在是个医生
jack's a doctor now,
Sun也生了孩子
and--and sun's,like, got her baby,
Kate和Aaron一起生活
and kate's got aaron.
老兄  冷静点
dude,be cool.
别看  我们被人盯上了
don't look, but we're being watched.
老兄
dude!
别担心  他和我一起的
oh,don't worry. he's with me.
-什么   -他开车送我来的  他没问题
- what?! - he's just driving me around. he's okay.
他才问题大了呢
that dude is far from okay.
当我第一次到这里时
when i first got locked up in here,
他就来找我  说他是大洋航空公司的
he showed up,claiming that he worked for oceanic air.
他是个魔鬼  你不该相信他的
he's evil! you should not be trusting that guy.
-听说我  -不不不  我不要听
please,just listen to me. no,no,no! i'm not listening to you!
-Hugo  求你了  听我说  -啦啦啦
- hugo,please,listen. - la,la,la,la,la
-我要进去了  我要进去  -Hugo
i wanna go back in. i wanna go back in. hugo--
我不会跟你去任何地方
no,i'm not going anywhere with you!
快走开  再见
go away! bye!
快离开
get out of here!
这是第三个了
that's three visits now.
Locke先生  你得动作快些
you may wanna step up your game,Mr. Locke,
否则我们的麻烦就大了
or we're all in serious trouble.
你到底为Widmore Matthew先生做什么
What exactly is it that you do for Mr. Widmore,Matthew?
你现在准备谈这个了吗
You're ready to talk about it now,huh?
John
John...
你不是真的打算 装作你不记得
You're not really gonna pretend you don't remember that
我是你出事故后待的那个医院的清洁工吧
I was an orderly in the hospital right after your accident?
正是我告诉你继续旅行
that I was the one who told you to go on your walkabout?
你搭的飞机在小岛上失事后
the same walkabout
你可以在岛上继续你的旅行
that put you on the plane that crashed on that island?
不
no.
我记得
I remember.
John  我帮人们去他们需要去的地方
I help people get to where they need to get to,John.
这就是我为Widmore先生干的活
that's what I do for Mr. Widmore.
洛杉矶  加利福尼亚
答案是不
the answer is no.
Kate  我认为你不明白
Kate,i don't think you understand--
不  你已经说得很明白
No,you made yourself perfectly clear.
如果我不回去  岛上的人都得死
Everyone on the island is gonna die if I don't go back.
答案是不
And the answer is no.
为什么  你不在乎他们吗
Why? Don't you care about them?
你有爱过别人吗  John
Have you ever been in love, John?
什么
What?
有时我会在想
I think about you sometimes.
你为什么这么希望待在那个岛上
I think about how desperate you were to stay on that island.
然后我就意识到
and then I realized...
这都是因为你不爱任何人
it was all because you didn't love anybody.
那不是真的
That's not true.
我曾经爱过
I loved someone...
某人
once.
她叫Helen
Her name was Helen.
怎么了
What happened?
只是  只是
it--it...
只是无果而终
it just didn't work out.
为什么无果  John
Why not,John?
我很生气
I was angry.
我被...
I was...
魔鬼附体了
ob-obsessed.
看看你走得多远
and look how far you've come.
我来帮你  Locke先生
Let me help you, Mr. Locke.
你找到她了吗
Did you find her?
找到谁
Find who?
Helen Norwood  我向你打听的女人
Helen Norwood--the woman I asked you about.
没找到  对不起
No, I didn't. I'm sorry.
三年的时间太长了
Three years is a long time.
很有可能她结婚了  改了名字
It's possible she got married, changed her name.
-也许她出国了  -你找到了其他人  所有人
- Maybe she moved out of state. - You found everyone else! all of them.
Sayid在一个不存在的地方  你都可以找到
Sayid was in the middle of nowhere,
而Helen只是搬家了  你就找不到
but you can't find Helen because she moved?
你的工作是带人们去他们要去的地方吗
Your job is to get people to where they need to get to?
那好  我要到她那里去
Well,I need to get to her.
圣莫尼卡  加利福尼亚
她出了什么事情
What happened to her?
她死于脑动脉瘤
She died of a brain aneurysm.
我很遗憾  Locke先生
I'm very sorry,Mr. Locke.
她爱我
She loved me.
如果我...
If I had just...
我们就可以在一起
we could've been together.
也许你可以
Maybe you could have.
任何事情都不会改变  她仍然会去世
That wouldn't change anything. she'd still be gone.
是吗
Would she?
Helen在她该去的地方
Helen is where she's supposed to be.
无论多么悲伤  她的路通向那里
as sad as it is, her path led here.
而你的路  无论你做过什么或要做什么
and you path,no matter what you did or what you do,
你的路通向小岛
your path leads back to the island.
你说这就像债务  无法逃避
You say that like it's all debt--inevitable.
Widmore先生告诉我
Mr. Widmore told me
Richard Alpert说你要死了
Richard Alpert said that you were going to die.
那么告诉我  John
So you tell me, John.
这是无可避免  抑或仅仅是个选择
is that inevitable, or is it a choice?
什么  你认为我想死吗
What,you think i wanna die?
怎么...
How is that...
你怎么可能认为这是种选择
How could you possibly think that's a choice?
我只是你的司机
I'm just your driver.
Matthew
Matthew!
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
Jack  你怎么找到我的
Jack,how did you find me?
你出了交通意外
You were in a car accident
被送进我的医院
and you were brought into my hospital.
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
我们必须回去
We have to go back.
当然
Of course.
当然我们得回去
Of course we do.
Jack  那些被我留下的人需要我们的帮助
Jack,the people I left behind need our help.
我们应该回去  因为那是我们的命运
We're supposed to go back-- because it's our destiny?
John  你还要这样和我说多少次
How many times are you gonna say that to me, John?
你怎么就不明白
How can you not see it?
他们可以送我去任何一个医院
of all the hospitals they could've brought me to,
却偏偏送到这里  你认为这不是命运
I end up here. you don't think that's fate?
你在洛杉矶西部出事故
Your car accident was on the west side of los angeles.
你被送进我在的医院不是命运  John
You being brought into my hospital isn't fate, John.
这是概率事件
It's probability.
你不明白  那不是个事故
You don't understand. it wasn't an accident.
有人要杀了我
Someone is trying to kill me.
为什么  为什么有人要杀你
Why? Why would someone try to kill you?
因为他们不想让我成功
Because they don't want me to succeed.
他们要阻止我
They wanna stop me.
他们不想让我回去 因为我很重要
They don't want me to get back because I'm important.
你就没抽空想想
Have you ever stopped to think
这些你认为自己很特殊的错觉 不是真实的
that these delusions that you're special aren't real?
可能你根本就没什么重要的
that maybe there's nothing important about you at all?
也许你就是个孤独的老头
maybe you are just a lonely old man
迫降到一个岛上
that crashed on an island.
仅此而已
that's it.
再见了  John
Good-bye,John.
你父亲向你问好
Your father says hello.
什么
What?
那个...那个让我移动小岛的人
A man--the man who told me to move the island--
那个教我如何把你们都带回去的人
The man who told me how to bring you all back--
让我向他儿子问好
He said to tell his son hello.
不可能是Sayid的父亲
It couldn't have been sayid's father,
也不是Hurley的父亲  只能是你的了
And it wasn't hurley's, so that leaves you.
他说他叫Christian
He said his name was christian.
我...
My...
我父亲死了
My father is dead.
我可看不出他死了
Well,he didn't look dead to me.
他三年前死在了澳大利亚
He died in australia three years ago.
我亲手把他放进灵柩
I put him in the coffin!
他死了
He's dead.
Jack  拜托  你必须回去
Jack,please, you have to come back!
你是唯一能说服大家的人
You're the only one who can convince the rest of 'em.
你要帮我  你应该要帮我
You have to help me! you're supposed to help me!
John  一切都结束了
John,it's over! it's done.
我们早已离开  而且无关紧要  所以你...
We left,and we were never important. so you...
你别再纠缠我
You leave me alone.
也别再纠缠其他人
And you leave the rest of 'em alone!
Jack  真希望当时你能相信我
Jack, I wish you had believe me.
Jack Shephard
John  John
John? john?
John  你在干什么
John,what are you doing?
等等  John  别动
wait,please. john,stop!
你怎么找到我的
H-how did you find me?
我派人监视Sayid
I have a man watching sayid.
我在监视他们所有人  保证他们安全
I'm watching all of them, keeping them safe.
你出现之后  他告诉了我
When you turned up, he called me.
谁...是谁...
Who... who...
你...你来这儿干什么
W-w-what are you doing here?
-John  冷静一点  -你想要我怎么样
- John,just calm down. - what do you want from me?!
-拜托  让我帮你... -快回答
- Please,let me help-- - Answer the question!
-我想保护你  -保护我
- I'm trying to protect you. - Protect me?
你杀了他
You shot him.
你杀了Abaddon
You killed Abaddon.
没错  是我杀的
Yes. Yes,I did.
但他迟早会杀了你的
But it was only a matter of time before he tried to kill you.
我只是想跟你谈谈
I was just trying to get to you,
但你驱车离开然后撞车了
But you drove off and crashed.
为什么  为什么要...
Why? Why would--
他是在为Charles Widmore效力
He was working for Charles Widmore.
-他是个危险分子  -不
- He's extremely dangerous. - No!
Widmore找到我  他救了我
Widmore came to me. He saved me.
不  John  他在利用你
No,John,he used you.
他一直在等待你的出现
He waited till you showed up
以便你助他一臂之力  得到小岛
So that you could help him get to the island.
正是由于Charles Widmore  我才要移动小岛
Charles Widmore is the reason I moved the island!
那样他就再也找不到它了
So that he could never find it again,
只有摆脱了他  你才能成为领导者
To keep him away so that you could lead.
你不能这么做
You can't do this.
如果你有个三长两短...
If anything happens to you...
John  你根本没意识到自己的重要性
John,you have no idea how important you are.
让我来帮你
Let me help you.
没人能帮我
There is no helping me.
我...
I'm...
-不  John  你不是  -我是
- No,John,you're not. - I am!
我无法说服他们任何人
I couldn't get any of them.
无法说服他们任何人跟我一起回去
I couldn't get a single one of them to come back with me.
我根本当不了领导者
I can't lead anyone.
Jack订了张机票
Jack booked a ticket.
什么
W-what?
一张从洛杉矶到悉尼的机票  今晚启程
A plane ticket from Los Angeles to Sydney,tonight.
明晨最早航班返回
Return trip first thing in the morning.
无论你和他说了什么  John  见效了
Whatever you said to him, John--it worked.
一旦你说服了Jack
And if you got jack,
其他人就好办了
You can get the rest of them.
John
John...
你不能死
You can't die.
你还有许多事情要做
You've got too much work to do.
我们还等着你重回小岛
We've gotta get you back to that island
你一定能成功的
So that you can do it.
求求你  John
Please,john.
来吧
Come on.
下来
Come down.
相信我们会成功的  John
I know we can do this, john.
你还没去找Sun呢
You haven't even been to Sun yet.
我们从她入手吧
Let's start with her.
不  我...
No. I...
我答应过Jin不会带她回去
I promised Jin that I wouldn't bring her back.
Jin还活着
Jin is alive?
对  对  但他不想让她知道
Yeah. Yeah. But he didn't want her to know.
他...他要我跟她说...
He--he wanted me to tell her that his...
他的尸体被冲上了沙滩
That his body washed up on the beach.
然后  他把结婚戒指给我作为证据
And,uh,he gave me his wedding ring to prove it.
好吧
All right.
答应了就不能食言
A promise is a promise.
谢谢
Thank you.
别客气
You're welcome.
来吧
Come on.
我们走
Let's go.
相信我们会成功的
I know we can do this.
一旦能把他们聚在一起...
Once we can get them all in the same place...
我不知道接下去该怎么办
I don't know where we go from there,
但总会想出办法来的
But we'll figure something out.
我知道该去找谁
I know where we go.
洛杉矶有个女人
There's a woman here in Los Angeles.
女人
A woman?
对  我不知道确切位置
Yeah,i don't know exactly where,
但找她应该不太难
But she shouldn't be that hard to find.
她叫...
Her name is--is,uh...
Eloise Hawking
Eloise Hawking.
Eloise Hawking  你确定吗
Eloise hawking? You sure?
对  没错  怎么了  你认识她吗
yeah,yeah. Yeah,why? Do you know her?
没错  John  我认识她
Yes. John. I know her.
我会想念你的  John
I'll miss you, John
一定会的
I really will
那个标志
That symbol
属于一个叫达摩计划的组织
Belongs to an organization called Dharma Initiative
他们之前在这里进行了一系列实验
They were conducting some experients here a while back
你怎么知道的
How do you know that
我在这个岛上待了一百多天  我知道很多事
I Spent more than a hundred days on this island I know a lot
一百多天
A hundred days
那么我们坠机的时候  你就已经在这里了
So when we crashed, you were already here
不  我离开过这里
No, no, I left
那是多久之前的事了
How long ago did you live
算起时间来  会弄晕了你的
It's timing It would just confuse you
那你有时怎么回来的呢
Well, how did you get back
老实说  我也参不透
To be honest, that part is a bit mystery to me
好吧  John Locke
Ok, John Locke,
我也有件参不透的事
I have a mystery too
没准能帮到你
Maybe it can help you with
愿闻其详
I am happy you try
在飞机上的时候  我旁边过道的另一侧
On the plane, I was sitting across the aisle
坐着一个卷发的大块头
from a really big guy with curly hair
当飞机狂震的时候  震得厉害
When the plane started shaking, really shaking
有巨大的噪音  还有一道强光
There was a big noise and a bright light
这个卷发的大块头就消失了
And this really big guy with curly hair was gone, man
毫不夸张  他消失了  不光有他
I mean literally gone. And it wasn't only him
我们当中还有人目击别的人也同样消失了
Some of us saw it happened to other people too
John Locke先生
So Mr. Jonh Locke
你知不知道到底发生了什么
Do you have an idea about what happened
我想我知道我是怎么来到这里的了
I think I might know how I came to be here
但我需要找到我的朋友
But that would involve me finding my friends.
你有乘客名单么
Do you have a passenger list
没有  我们起飞后机长拿走了
No, the pilot took it when we went off
每个人都核实了
And everyone is accounted for,
所有人  除了那些消失了的
All the people, other than the ones who disappeared
是的  另外除了那些受伤的人
Yeah, yeah, except people who got hurt
有人受伤么
People got hurt
你认识他
You know him
是的
Yeah
他是那个杀了我的人
He is the man who killed me